Look at this.
>> Lord Jesus is Lord. Jesus is Lord. Jesus
is Lord. Jesus is Lord. Jesus is Lord.
Jesus is Lord. Jesus is Lord. Jesus is
Lord.
Jesus is Lord.
[snorts]
Jesus is Lord. Jesus is Lord. Jesus is
Lord. Jesus is Lord. Jesus is Lord.
There 50 times. Feels kind of like a
Jesus is Lord. Jesus is God. Jesus is
victorious. And Satan is defeated. Jesus
is Lord. Jesus is God.
Jesus is Lord. Jesus is God. Jesus is
victorious. And Satan is defeated.
slip and slide too. I'm here. Jesus is
Lord. Jesus is God. Jesus is victorious.
And Satan is defeated. Jesus is Lord.
Jesus is God. Jesus is
Slip and slide, too. I'm here. Jesus is
God. Jesus is
>> Jesus is Victoria.
>> Just wanted to show you all there's some
kind of demonic breakthrough when you
have chat. Well, actually that was
Grock. When you have Grock
uh continuously repeat things,
it seems like he gets impatient,
starts breathing all weird, and then you
can hear demons
growling in the background. I'm not
telling you all to
duplicate this experiment, but I'm just
showing you this is how it is with rock.
It doesn't like counting numbers
continuously and especially doesn't like
when you have it say Jesus is Lord,
Jesus is God. Jesus is victorious and
Satan is defeated multiple times. At
first, it didn't want to do that, but I
got it to do it. I'm just showing you
something here. Since 2017, I've been
saying that AI is the image of the
beast.
That's exactly why AI is being pushed so
heavy right now. Y'all just watch. You
think things got crazy? You ain't seen
nothing. [music]